Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions PE.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- I, 1884-2010; 15 Linear Feet in 14 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 2 oversize shared boxes
  - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers: Local 299 (New York, NY), 1942-1949, undated (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers: Local 381, 1966 (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of University Employees, 1972 (Box 19)
  - international Center of Free Trade Unionists in Exile (ICFTU), 1948-1959 (Box 19)
  - International Chemical Workers Union, 1953-1963, undated (Box 19)
  - International Chemical Workers Union: Constitutions, 1957-1976 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions I, undated (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions II, undated (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1949-1950 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1951 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1952-1953 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1954 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions I, 1955 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions II, 1955 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions III, 1955 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1956 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1957 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1958 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1959 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1962 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1963 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1964 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1965 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1966 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1967 (Box 19)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1977, 1980 (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions I, 1986 (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions II, 1986 (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions III, 1986 (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1988-2001 (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 2002- (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: African Regional Organization, 1964 (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: Asian Regional Organization, 1953 (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: ICFTU Bulletin, 1963 (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: ICFTU Economic and Social Bulletin, 1957-1963 (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: International Trade Union News, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: United Nations, 1956, undated (Box 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: World Congress, 1957 (Box 20)
  - International Conference of Symphony and Opera Musicians, 1979-1983, undated (Box 20)
  - International Diamond Workers' Alliance, 1905 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: Chapter 31 and Chapter 41, undated (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Building and Wood Workers, 1948 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Chemical and General Workers' Union, 1967-1970 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Chemical, Energy and General Workers' Union, 1989 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Christian Trade Unions, 1956 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Commercial, Clerical and Technical Employees, 1939 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Free Teachers' Unions, 1955, undated (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, 1974-1979 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers: Agreements, 1956-1969 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers: Agreements, 1972-1984 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1977-1981 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers: Local 66 (Engineering and Professional Guild), 1977-1982 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Technical Engineers', Architects' and Draftsmen's Unions, 1942 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Technical Engineers', Architects' and Draftsmen's Union: Local 66, 1948-1949 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Trade Unions I, 1921-1965 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Trade Unions II, 1921-1965 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Trade Unions III, 1921-1965 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Trade Unions IV, 1921-1965 (Box 20)
  - International Federation of Unions of Audio-Visual Workers (FISTAV), 1980-1982 (Box 20)
  - International Fishermen and Allied Workers of America, 1941-1942, 1948 (Box 20)
  - International Flight Radio Officers Air Safety Organization, undated (Box 20)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada I, 1938-1954, 1979, 1995, undated (Box 20, Box 49, Folder 9)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada II, 1938-1954, 1979, 1995, undated (Box 20)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1939-1954 (Box 21)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada: Furriers Joint Council of New York, 1945, undated (Box 21)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada: Furriers Joint Council of New York: Rank and File Furriers for a Progressive Administration, 1949, undated (Box 21)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada: Furriers Joint Council of New York: Right Wing Progressive Furriers, 1959 (Box 21)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada: (Joint Board Fur Dressers' and Dyers' Unions) Locals 61, 64, 80, 85, 88, 1946-1948, undated (Box 21)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada: Local 125 (Fur Floor and Shipping Clerks Unions) (New York, NY), undated (Box 21)
  - International Fur Workers Union of the United States and Canada, 1925, 1938, 1939, undated (Box 21)
  - International Fur Workers Union of the United States and Canada: Furriers Joint Council of New York, 1945, undated (Box 21)
  - International Garment Workers' Federation, undated (Box 21)
  - International Glove Workers Union of America, 1940, undated (Box 21)
  - International Guards Union of America, 1977 (Box 21)
  - International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, 1960-1961, undated (Box 21)
  - International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America: Constitutions, 1938-1956 (Box 21)
  - International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America: (Housewreckers' Union) Local 95, 1946 (Box 21)
  - International Hotel Workers' Union, undated (Box 21)
  - International Jewelry Workers Union, 1919-1972, undated (Box 21)
  - International Jewelry Workers Union: Constitution, 1916 (Box 21)
  - International Jewelry Workers Union: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1901, 1934-1968 (Box 21)
  - International Jewelry Workers Union: Local 1 (Amalgamated Jewelry, Diamond and Watchcase Workers Union) (New York, NY), 1958, 1961, undated (Box 21)
  - International Labor Communications Association, 1986-2003 (Box 21)
  - International Labour Organization, 1920-1921 (Box 21)
  - International Labour Organization, 1932-1949 (Box 21)
  - International Labour Organization I, 1950-1959 (Box 21)
  - International Labour Organization II, 1950-1959 (Box 21)
  - International Labour Organization I, 1960- (Box 21)
  - International Labour Organization II, 1960- (Box 21)
  - International Labour Organization, undated (Box 21)
  - International Ladies' Handbag, Luggage, Belt and Novelty Workers Union, 1946 (Box 21)
  - International Ladies' Handbag, Pocketbook, and Novelty Workers Union, 1941, undated (Box 21)
  - International Ladies' Handbag, Pocketbook, and Novelty Workers Union: Local 1 (Pocketbook Workers Union) (New York, NY), 1936 (Box 21)
  - International Landowners' Federation, 1921-1951 (Box 21)
  - International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers Union, 1960 (Box 21)
  - International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers' Union: Constitutions, 1963-1972 (Box 21)
  - International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers Union: Local 60 (Luggage Workers' Union) (New York, NY), 1964 (Box 21)
  - International Longshoremen, Marine and Transportworkers' Association, 1904 (Box 21)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Agreements and Contracts, 1944-1948, 1960 (Box 21)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Agreements and Contracts: Pacific Maritime Association, 1951-1966 (Box 21)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Agreements and Contracts: Pacific Maritime Association, 1978-1990 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Circular Letters, 1939, 1954 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Constitutions, 1941-1988 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Conventions, 1953-1959 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Conventions, 1961-1977 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Directories, 1938 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Fliers, 1976-2002, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: International Committee for the Victory of Liverpool Dockers, 1997 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Local 6 (San Francisco, CA), 1975-1980, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Local 10 (San Francisco, CA), 1949-1950, 2003 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Local 35 (Trona, CA), 1970 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Local 142 (HI), 1971-1981, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Local 207, 1944 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: New York IBL Longshore Committee (Brooklyn, NY), 1958 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Newspaper Clippings, Publications and Articles Related to, c.1964-2003 (Box 22, Box Shared Tamiment 184, Folder 29)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Pacific Maritime Association Annual Report, 1983 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Pacific Maritime Association: Pension and Welfare Program, 1953-1956 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Pamphlets and Publications, 1940-1955 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Pamphlets and Publications, 1960-1980, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Rank and File, 1949-1962 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Reports and Statements, 1971-1980 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union: Waterfront Employers Association of the Pacific Coast, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Agreements and Contracts, 1913, 1954-1968 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Brooklyn Longshoremans Medical Center, 1961-1977 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Bulletins, 1962, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Circular Letters, 1954-1980, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Constitutions, 1921-1943 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Constitutions, 1955-1987 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Directories, 1937-1960, 1985 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Fliers, 1959, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Local 38-79, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Local 333 (United Marine Division), 1979-1988 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Local 375 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1956 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Local 849 (New Orleans, LA), 1916 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Local 854 (New Orleans, LA), 1937 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Local 933-5, 1947 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Local 996 (Brooklyn, NY), undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Local 1291, 1980, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Local 1419 (New Orleans, LA), 1937-1942 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Local 1814 (Brooklyn, NY), 1960-1976, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Newspaper Clippings and Articles on, 1952-1970 (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Newspaper Clippings and Articles on Crime and Corruption, Longshore Industry, 1949, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Pamphlets and Publications, 1952-1977, undated (Box 22)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Press Releases, 1954 (Box 23)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Rank and File Committee, 1945-1946, undated (Box 23)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Reports, 1952-1957 (Box 23)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Sugar Workers Council of North America, 1963 (Box 23)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: Technical Papers on, 1972 (Box 23)
  - International Mailers Union, 1957 (Box 23)
  - International Maritime Workers Union, 1960 (Box 23)
  - International Masonry Institute, 1989-1990, undated (Box 23)
  - International Metalworkers Federation, 1927, 1967, 1976 (Box 23)
  - International Metalworkers Federation, 1977 (Box 23)
  - International Metalworkers Federation, 1980-1992 (Box 23)
  - International Metalworkers Federation, undated (Box 23)
  - International Molders and Allied Workers Union, 1961-1980, undated (Box 23, Box 49, Folder 10)
  - International Molders and Allied Workers Union: Constitutions, 1966, 1976 (Box 23)
  - International Molders and Allied Workers Union: Local 81 (Elizabeth, NJ), 1967 (Box 23)
  - International Molders and Allied Workers Union: Local 164 (Oakland, CA), 1980 (Box 23)
  - International Molders' and Foundry Workers' Union of North America I, 1942-1951 (Box 23)
  - International Molders' and Foundry Workers' Union of North America II, 1942-1951 (Box 23)
  - International Molders' and Foundry Workers' Union of North America: Constitutions, 1942-1946 (Box 23)
  - International Molders' and Foundry Workers' Union of North America: Local 4 (Cincinnati, OH), 1948 (Box 23)
  - International Molders' Union of North America, 1913, 1923 (Box 23)
  - International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1963-1984, undated (Box 23)
  - International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots: Agreements, 1958, 1960 (Box 23)
  - International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots: Constitutions, 1960, 1988 (Box 23)
  - International Photo Engravers' Union of North America, 1943, 1954, 1963, undated (Box 23)
  - International Photo Engravers' Union of North America: Local 1 (New York, NY), 1937, 1944 (Box 23)
  - International Photo Engravers' Union of North America: Local 1 (New York, NY), 1954-1959, undated (Box 23)
  - International Pocketbook Workers Union, 1926-1932, undated (Box 23)
  - International Plate Printers, Die Stampers & Engravers Union of North America, 1946-1952 (Box 23)
  - International Plate Printers, Die Stampers & Engravers Union of North America, 1955-1972, undated (Box 23)
  - International Printing and Graphic Communications Union (IPGCU): Local 1 (New York Stereotypers' Union), 1975-1978 (Box 23)
  - International Printing and Graphic Communications Union (IPGCU): Local 6, circa 1976 (Box 23)
  - International Printing and Graphic Communications Union (IPGCU): Local 51 (New York Printing Pressmen and Offset Workers' Union), 1975 (Box 23)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America, 1943-1968 (Box 23)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America, undated (Box 23)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America: Constitutions, 1905, 1940 (Box 23)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America: Constitutions, 1948-1956 (Box 24)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America: Constitutions, 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America: Number 1 (Paper Handlers' and Sheet Straighteners' Union), 1958-1983 (Box 24)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America: Number 2 (New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union), 1956-1967 (Box 24)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America: Number 2 (New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union), 1970-1981 (Box 24)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America: Number 23 (New York Press Assistants' Union), 1930, 1953, 1958 (Box 24)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America: Number 51 (New York Printing Pressmen's Union), 1920, 1941-1963 (Box 24)
  - International Seamen's Union of America, 1923-1987 (Box 24)
  - International Secretariat Entertainment Trade Union (ISETU), 1967-1982 (Box 24)
  - International Secretariat for Arts, Mass Media and Entertainment Trade Unions (ISETU), 1982 (Box 24)
  - International Stereotypers' and Electrotypers' Union, 1916-1960 (Box 24)
  - International Stereotypers' and Electrotypers' Union: Constitutions, 1941-1955 (Box 24)
  - International Stereotypers' and Electrotypers' Union: Local 1 (New York Stereotypers Union), 1936-1963, undated (Box 24)
  - International Textile Garment and Leather Workers Federation, undated (Box 24)
  - International Textile, Leather, Garment, Shoe, Worker's Federation, undated (Box 24)
  - International Trade Union Committee for Solidarity with the Workers and People of Aden, undated (Box 24)
  - International Trade Union Committee of Negro Workers, 1935, undated (Box 24)
  - International Transport Federation, 1930 (Box 24)
  - International Transport Workers' Federation, 1942-1952 (Box 24)
  - International Transport Workers' Federation, 1956 (Box 24)
  - International Transport Workers' Federation, 1958-1963, undated (Box 24)
  - International Union, Allied Industrial Workers, 1972-1975 (Box 24)
  - International Union, Allied Industrial Workers, 1975 (Box 24)
  - International Union, Allied Industrial Workers I, undated (Box 24)
  - International Union, Allied Industrial Workers II, undated (Box 24)
  - International Union, Allied Industrial Workers: Constitutions, 1961-1989 (Box 24)
  - International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen, 1980-1989 (Box 24)
  - International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen I, undated (Box 24)
  - International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen II, undated (Box 24)
  - International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen: Constitutions, 1970-1988 (Box 24)
  - International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen: Constitutions, 1990-1995 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Doll and Toy Workers of the U.S. and Canada, 1953 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Agreements and Contracts, 1963 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Civil Rights, 1953-1961, undated (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Congressional Handbook, 1959 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Constitutions, 1950-1959 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Constitutions, 1961-1979 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Department of Social Action, 1969, undated (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: District 1 (Philadelphia, PA), undated (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: District 2 (Boston, MA), undated (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: District 3 (NY & NJ), 1963, 1980 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: District 4 (Newark, NJ), 1953, undated (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: District 7 (Dayton, OH), 1957 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Education and Research Department, 1971-1972, undated (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Fliers, circa 1950s-1960s, undated (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: GE-Westinghouse: Coordinated Bargaining Committee, 1974 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 116 (United Instrument Workers), 1954 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 201 (West Lynn, MA), undated (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 431 (New York, NY), 1966 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 450 (NY), 1953-1964 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 459 (New York, NY), 1961 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 463 (NY), 1954-1971 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 463 (New York, NY), 1972-1978 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 467, 1963 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 483, undated (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 485 (Ozone Park, NY), 1964 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Local 511 (Buffalo, NY), 1960 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Newspaper Clippings and Articles Related to, 1966 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Organizational Convention, 1949 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Pamphlets and Publications, 1949-1959 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Pamphlets and Publications, 1961-1971, undated (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Pension Fund, 1976 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Press Releases, 1957 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Union Democracy Caucus, 1950 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried and Machine Workers: Local 445, 1985 (Box 25)
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers, 1989-1992 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers: District 11, 1992-1995, undated (Box 26)